Hello guys!
I am in Budapest and I'm so excited to be here.
I'm visiting with my friend Mattea, but she hasn't arrived.
She lives in the Netherlands, but we're meeting in Budapest.
It's going to be a girl's trip and I'm so excited.
I didn't realize that it was going to be this warm until I was packing yesterday.
Thankfully I brought a lot of skirts and tank tops because the heat is insane.
Like for September I thought it was gonna be like fall weather.
It's currently 1 p.m which is so nice.
It was like an early flight.
Mate will arrive in a couple of hours and I have arrived in the city center.
It took about one hour to take the bus from the airport to the city center.
I'm currently walking to our Airbnb and I thought I should start the vlog.
So yeah, I'm so excited!
Welcome to our Airbnb.
I am seeing this all for the first time, like you guys.
Wow, that's a very spacious bedroom and it has a bathtub.
This is huge and here is the bathroom it feels
So good to finally have arrived here into the airbnb and like I need to take this shirt off it's
Way too warm I brought my leather jacket with me which I think was a mistake I thought that maybe
I could use it during the evenings but I checked my phone It's 26 degrees.
I thought that that would be like in July, but I love the heat, so I am not complaining.
I am gonna do my makeup, and then I'm going to head out.
I am getting a bit hungry, so I was thinking about going to a croissant bakery that is close by.
You guys recommended this place, and I am in the need of a cup of coffee and some croissant.
I'm not gonna put on a lot of makeup just a little bit to freshen up but I was thinking
About like telling you guys a little bit about this trip.
I feel like I haven't really told you guys anything.
We are staying here for three nights and we are leaving on a Saturday.
I would have wanted to stay here until Sunday but the flight was just ridiculously expensive so it just didn't
Really make sense.
Mattia is actually also from Iceland.
We didn't really know each other when we lived in Iceland but just recently, like a couple of months
Ago, we met for a cup of coffee.
I feel like we immediately clicked and she is just so genuine and sweet and we get along so nicely.
It was honestly kind of random how we started talking about going on a trip together but neither of us
Had visited this city before so it was just so ideal to go
Together.
I am not gonna change outfits.
I'm just gonna wear this one.
I just changed the top because this one is a little bit nicer since I'm not gonna be wearing this
One probably.
I'm gonna keep it in my bag in case anything.
It's just better to have it.
Mathea is almost here.
I'm waiting for her in front of our Airbnb.
Be.
Matteo just got dressed and we're gonna head out.
We're kind of matching today.
Like coordinating our outfits together.
I like it.
I'm
Gonna try on these Adam Sandler shorts.
I think they're kind of cute.
Matta just bought a leather jacket!
I love it!
I love the color.
It's so pretty!
Right?
Yeah!
I'm very happy with it.
My grandpa loves the Beatles and I know that he would love for me to wear this
One.
And I was thinking about this one for Helgi but I'm gonna try it on anyways
It's
Dinner time and we have decided to go to a restaurant called Tati and we looked at the menu and
They have some traditional Hungarian food like goulash and some of you actually recommended to try chicken
Paprikash and I'm a little bit excited to try that.
And we're so hungry!
Oh my god so hungry!
So good to sit down!
Good morning!
It's 8 30.
We just woke up.
Matta is taking a shower.
By the way guys, I tried the chicken paprikas yesterday.
It was really good.
I have to admit, I was a little bit skeptical if my chicken was like undercooked, because it was so
Soft, and the lighting in the restaurant was a little bit dark, and I felt like it was a little
Bit pink, also because of the orange like sauce.
So I was like kind of scared.
So I asked like the waiter and he told me that like it's supposed to look like this.
And apparently they sous vide it.
I don't know how you say it.
Yeah, it's called sous vide.
It's basically like where you put the meat in like a plastic bag, I think.
And it's like in water for many, many hours.
I think he said like 16 hours or something, if I remember correctly.
So no salmonella for me, but yeah, it was delicious and we sat there until I think like
11.
We were the last people out of that restaurant.
We were talking so much and we were just having such a great time.
So we are gonna have breakfast somewhere.
I'm not sure where.
You guys recommended so many places and they all look amazing.
When I was packing, I like decided on an outfit that I was gonna wear today but since the weather
Is so amazing I'm like oof I'm not sure if I can wear it it's like this knit maybe
I can wear some of the things that I thrifted yesterday I'm going to try on these pants
I have these really cute high heels.
They are from Billy Bee.
I'm not sure if I'm feeling this outfit.
I've been struggling a bit to decide what to wear.
I don't know.
I feel like I didn't pack properly.
It's always the thing with me.
I'm wearing this t-shirt that I thrifted yesterday.
We are hunting for some breakfast, trying to find a nice
Cafe.
Let's see where we end up.
A little outfit check.
There was a guy that stopped me like on the street and he wanted to take
Some pictures of my outfit.
I was kind of flattered.
He recommended us to go to like a vintage store that's close by.
So we're gonna go and have a look there.
Okay, slay queen.
I think it's like the perfect sweater for winter, like the turtleneck.
And it's pure wool, which is nice.
I found this really cute top.
It reminds me of Orsunt Iris.
I'm not sure how you pronounce the brand but We
Are
At like a bar or a pub But they're like all around So you can like choose different ones
Yeah, it's super cool.
It's called Simpla Kert.
So many of you guys recommended this place.
They have 55,000 reviews on Google Maps.
That's insane for like a pub.
Yeah.
So we bought some Prosecco.
Cheers.
Nice.
Prosecco Some Prosecco.
Cheers!
Nice!
We are gonna do some more exploring and we are gonna rent bikes.
We just figured out we downloaded some app because the Airbnb host offered us some
Bikes.
So we are gonna bike.
I'm kind of stressed out.
I don't know how it's gonna go, but hopefully it's gonna be okay.
Okay, run now.
Successful!
Oh my god!
It unlocked.
Now it's just a question how I do with my bags.
So
Apparently
Is Budapest divided into two cities into one.
I see it here on Google.
It says that the Hungarian capital is usually divided into two.
Buda and Past.
And we have been in the past during the time that we have been here So we biked over a
Bridge and it was so beautiful But now we are struggling a little bit to return the bikes
Oh la la Oh okay I think our Airbnb is a bit pissed But he needs to call then right?
Yeah He needs to call the customer service because we can't return the bikes The time is ticking and we
Need to pay extra fee I think it's gonna be okay.
Hopefully.
We are walking towards the Buddha castle and we're gonna see what's going on over there.
Apparently there's a wine festival but we don't know.
We're just gonna try and see what's going on.
So
We've
Been exploring the buddha area of the city today and it is absolutely beautiful we didn't have much time because
Of the bicycle problem but we really enjoyed this area of the city.
The waitress yesterday told us that this area is a little bit more like posh and there is more like
Nature here and yeah it's kind of different.
You can like feel the difference between like these two areas.
We are walking back to the pest area of the city and the sunset is beautiful and
We are going to walk over the bridge.
We are on our way to go to a restaurant.
I don't remember what it's called, but we walked past it yesterday and it looked very like authentic and very
Cozy But they didn't have a table available yesterday.
So we booked it for today, but we are currently like getting a bit late So we need to walk
Fast
So there were some slight change of plans.
We ended up going to a Mexican place because it looked so good and we were just really craving it.
And like yesterday we went to a Hungarian place so we wanted to change it up and we are very
Happy with our decision because like this place is huge and like the vibe really nice.
Love it!
We are in bed now and we're gonna put on a face mask.
Super hydrating brightening milky serum.
Oh they're very gooey.
This feels so good.
I love.
Good morning.
We just got ready and we are both wearing like our latest thrift finds.
Like this dress is so gorgeous.
We are just ready for the day.
We're going to grab some bikes and a bike to a bakery.
It's called Louie.
And then we are going to visit the Hungarian parliament.
So yeah, we're excited for the day.
Stay tuned.
Woohoo!
This
Place is amazing, like the pastry, wow.
She ordered pistachio croissant and then cookie, very excited to try it and
Sandwich or like a grilled cheese.
Really really good.
Is incredible if you like coffee the coffee here is so good mm-hmm really really good I have a nice
Latte here and it's amazing Come then.
Okay guys, we are on a mission.
We are going to go to like a hot air balloon.
If it's possible, if we will find it.
Because we were at a restaurant and the waitress recommended going on a hot air balloon.
And we saw it also yesterday in the air.
And it looked so much fun.
Amazing.
So we are very excited.
It's a bucket list thing.
Yes, very much so.
If we manage, we are crossing our fingers.
Yay!
Then it's a bucket list thing.
Hopefully we'll find it.
Sadly, the air balloon is not running now because the wind is a little bit too strong apparently.
But maybe later today they will open it.
So we're not sure what we're gonna do.
But we have booked a river cruise with unlimited prosecco because so many of
You guys were like this was the highlight of my trip.
So we booked it yesterday, we were like we need to do it.
So we're going there at 7 and now it's like 3 and we're gonna go home in the meantime and
Switch outfits and we're gonna be a little bit like fancy.
We wanted to try a lankos.
So many of you guys said that we need to try it and there was like this specific place that
We had to try.
So I think we are gonna go there and then bike home, get ready and go to the river
Cruise.
Okay guys, they just opened the hot air balloon.
We're going.
It was so much fun in the hot air balloon.
I don't know what you said.
Yeah, it was just amazing to get an overview of the city and we could see like the thermal baths
Because we didn't Have the time to go there.
We were kind of sad because it looks so nice So it was kind of cool to see it from
The above and maybe next time in Budapest We will go there and try it.
Yeah now we're just heading to the place to have langos
Okay guys, the weather is insane.
We couldn't get seats in the shadow so we're just gonna work with this but time for a taste test.
We got the most like popular one which is sour cream and cheese.
Like my first reaction is that the cheese is like raw.
It's not like melted.
That's very interesting.
Okay.
Oh my god, that's actually really good.
We are back home.
We are kind of running late.
I just hopped into the shower.
I like removed my makeup except my mascara.
I am so excited to wear this dress.
It's like really long and it is absolutely stunning.
It's from a brand called Arsinaori.
I think you pronounce it like that.
So I'm gonna jump into this dress.
I just redid my makeup and I think we are ready to go.
I'm gonna show you the dress.
Thank you.
It's
The next morning and we are heading to the airport leaving budapest for now but honestly guys we truly
Had the best time ever the city is absolutely beautiful and it's like a lot bigger than I expected.
It is very much alive and like I just love the vibe here and we honestly like really loved it
Here but I would definitely want to come here again.
Biking around the city has been so much fun and like we ate so much good food, we were able
To vintage shop and yeah it was just so much fun.
We're heading to the airport now.
Oh we're so sad but thank you guys so much for watching.
I will link Mattia's Instagram and TikTok in the bio.
So go follow her.
She is starting her like a little bit content creation.
So go and give her a follow.
She's so good.
But thank you guys for watching.
I'll see you in my next video.
Bye.